<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.elf-dissector</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>ELF Dissector</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">ELF Dissector</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">ELF-dissector</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Análise do ELF</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">ELF-dissektor</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">ELF Dissector</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxELF Dissectorxx</name>
  <summary>Static analysis tool for ELF files</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Eina d'anàlisi estàtica per als fitxers ELF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Statisch analysehulpmiddel voor ELF-bestanden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Ferramenta de análise estática de ficheiros ELF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Statiskt analysverktyg av ELF-filer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Інструмент статичного аналізу файлів ELF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxStatic analysis tool for ELF filesxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>ELF Dissector is useful if you need to do one or more of the following tasks:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'ELF Dissector és útil si cal fer una o més de les tasques següents:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">ELF Dissector is nuttig als u een of meer van de volgende taken moet doen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">A Análise do ELF é útil se precisar de fazer uma ou mais das seguintes tarefas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">ELF-dissektor är användbar om du behöver utföra en eller fler av följande uppgifter:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">ELF Dissector стане у пригоді, коли вам захочеться виконати одне з таких завдань:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxELF Dissector is useful if you need to do one or more of the following tasks:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Inspecting forward and backward dependencies, on library and symbol level.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Inspeccionar les dependències cap endavant i cap enrere, a nivell de biblioteca i símbols.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Inspecteren van voorwaartse en achterwaartse afhankelijkheden, op niveau van bibliotheek en symbool.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Inspecção das dependências anteriores e posteriores, ao nível da biblioteca e do símbolo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inspektera framåt- och bakåtberoenden på biblioteks- och symbolnivå.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Інспектування прямих і зворотних залежностей на рівні бібліотек і символів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxInspecting forward and backward dependencies, on library and symbol level.xx</li>
      <li>Identifying load-time performance bottlenecks such as expensive static constructors or excessive relocations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Identificació de colls d'ampolla de rendiment en temps de càrrega com constructors estàtics cars o relocacions excessives.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Identificeren van prestatie-bottlenecks bij laden zoals dure statische constructors of overdreven relocaties.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Identificação de constrangimentos de performance no carregamento, como construtores estáticos dispendiosos ou realocações excessivas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Identifiera prestandaflaskhalsar vid laddning, såsom kostsamma statiska konstruktorer eller överdrivna relokeringar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Визначення вузьких місць у швидкодії під час завантаження, зокрема вартісних статичних конструкторів або надмірних пересувань даних.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIdentifying load-time performance bottlenecks such as expensive static constructors or excessive relocations.xx</li>
      <li>Size profiling of ELF files.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Anàlisi del rendiment de mida dels fitxers ELF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Profileren van grootte van ELF-bestanden.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Análise do tamanho dos ficheiros ELF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Storleksprofilering av ELF-filer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Профілювання за розміром файлів ELF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSize profiling of ELF files.xx</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Main features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques principals:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Hoofdkenmerken:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades principais:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Huvudfunktionalitet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Основні можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMain features:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>ELF structure browser.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Explorador de l'estructura ELF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">ELF-structuurbrowser.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Navegação pela estrutura ELF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">ELF-strukturbläddrare.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Навігація структурою ELF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxELF structure browser.xx</li>
      <li>Tree map visualization of the size of the various parts of an ELF file.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Visualització de mapa d'arbre de la mida de parts diverses d'un fitxer ELF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Visualisatie van boomstructuur van de grootte van de verschillende onderdelen van een ELF-bestand.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Visualização em árvore do tamanho das diversas componentes de um ficheiro ELF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visualisering av storleken för de olika delarna av en ELF-file med en trädavbildning.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Візуалізація у вигляді деревоподібної структури для розмірів різних частин файла ELF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTree map visualization of the size of the various parts of an ELF file.xx</li>
      <li>Relocation heatmap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Mapa de calor de les relocacions.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Relocatie heatmap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">'Mapa de calor' das realocações.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Färgdiagram för relokeringar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">«Теплова» карта пересувань.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxRelocation heatmap.xx</li>
      <li>Built-in disassembler for x86 and AArch64.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Desassemblador incorporat per a x86 i AArch64.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ingebouwde disassembler voor x86 en AArch64.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Descodificação para Assembly incorporada para o x86 e o AArch64.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inbyggd disassembler för x86 och AArch64.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вбудований дизасемблер для x86 та AArch64.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxBuilt-in disassembler for x86 and AArch64.xx</li>
      <li>Browser for data type memory layouts extracted from DWARF debug information.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Navegador de les disposicions de memòria per tipus de dada extretes de la informació de depuració DWARF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Browser voor indeling geheugen van het type gegevens uitgepakt uit DWARF-debuginformatie.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Navegação pelos diferentes formatos de memória para dados extraídos a partir da informação de depuração DWARF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Bläddrare för minneslayout av datatyper extraherad från DWARF avlusningsinformation.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Навігатор компонуваннями пам'яті для типів даних на основі діагностичних даних DWARF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxBrowser for data type memory layouts extracted from DWARF debug information.xx</li>
      <li>Forward and backward dependency viewer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Visualitzador de les dependències cap endavant i cap enrere.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Viewer voor voorwaartse en achterwaartse afhankelijkheid.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Visualização das dependências anteriores e posteriores.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visning av framåt- och bakåtberoenden.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Прямий і зворотний перегляд залежностей.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxForward and backward dependency viewer.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.elf-dissector.desktop</launchable>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>elf-dissector</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
